(Sheldon(Knock, knock, knock):)This is for you.
(Penny:)Hello, Sheldon.
(Howard:)Hi.
- What is this?
- It's a questionnaire I devised.
(Sheldon:)I'm having some difficulty bonding
with a colleague at work...
(Sheldon:)...so I'm doing a little research to better
understand why my current friends like me.
(Penny:)Yes, well, that is a good question.
(Penny:)But is this really the best way
to figure it out?
(Sheldon:)I agree.
(Sheldon:)The social sciences are largely hokum.
(Sheldon:)But short of putting electrodes in your brain
and monitoring your response...
(Sheldon:)...to my companionship,
this is the best I can do.
Okay, question one:
"Rank the following aspects
of Sheldon Cooper in order of appeal:
(Penny:)Intelligence,
ruthless attention to hygiene...
...playfulness, Java-applet writing"?
(Sheldon:)I know. I may have started off
with a fairly obvious one.
(Sheldon:)An aspect
of my most appealing trait:
(Penny:)playfulness.
Why don't you rank that number one?
You're on your own for the rest.